izettle.com 2013-01-17

# Privacy Policy - iZettle

### Request an invite!

You can sign up for iZettle in Sweden, Norway, Denmark, Finland, the UK, Germany and Spain. 

We're also coming soon to even more countries. Would you like it to be yours? Sign up here and we'll keep you in the loop!

This privacy policy explains how we, iZettle AB, process and use personal data provided to, and collected by, us through the registration on izettle.com (the Website) and in connection with use of your iZettle to take chip card payments and to keep track of the card payments you take with your iZettle (the Services). By accepting this Privacy Policy you consent to our use and processing of your personal data in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Please read it carefully before you proceed.

#### 1\. What personal data do we collect?

#### 1.1 Information you provide to us

When you register as a private person we collect certain personal information which includes your name, address, email address, personal identity number, date of birth and phone number.

When you register as a company we collect certain information which includes your company name, registration number, type of business, address, phone number and name, date of birth, address and phone number of your company signatory.

In order for you to make transactions and use our Services we collect information regarding your bank account which includes your account number, clearing number and the name of the account holder.

#### 1.2 Information we collect automatically

In order to confirm and verify your bank account and your identity and manage our risk we receive additional information about you from third party verification services and credit bureaus. Such information may include credit rating, risk class, risk forecast, credit limit, legal form, share capital, VAT number, domicile, places of business, calculated annual revenue, date of registration, board of directors, summary of annual accounts and key ratio, record of non-payment and debt with the enforcement service.

When you use our Services we record your account transactions, [transaction location, payment card numbers, payment card holders and information about financial institutions where you conduct business.]

We may also use a variety of technologies that automatically or passively collect information about how our Services are accessed and used. Such information may include: IP address or other unique identifier for the computer, mobile device, technology or other device you use to access our Website or use our Services, browser type and operating system. It may also include information about your activities whilst on the Website and when using our Services as well as information about other websites that you have visited either before or after you have entered onto the Website. For example, if you link your account to Facebook, or use other third-party sites or services in conjunction with your account, we may collect information related to your use of those third party sites.

#### 2\. How do we collect information?

We use a variety of technical methods such as cookies and web beacons to collect information.

**Cookies.** Cookies are data files placed on your computer, mobile device, technology or other device when it is used to visit the Website. The Website uses both session cookies which disappear when you shut down your web browser and persistent cookies that are saved on your computer. Cookies are used for security purposes, to facilitate site navigation and to personalise your experience while visiting our Websites. Cookies allow us to collect technical and navigational information, such as browser type, time spent on our Website and pages visited. Cookies allow us to select which of our advertisements or offers are most likely to appeal to you and display them while you are on the Website. You always have the option of disabling cookies using your browser preferences. However, please be aware that some features of the Website may not function properly or may be slower if you refuse cookies.

**Web Beacons.** Small graphic images or other web programming code called web beacons, may be included in the Website and e-mail messages. Web beacons or similar technologies may be used for a number of purposes, including, without limitation, to count visitors to the Website, to monitor how users navigate the Website, to count how many e-mails that were sent were actually opened or to determine whether content sent was actually viewed.

#### 3.How do we use your Personal Data?

Information you submit to us will be used for a variety of purposes such as, for example: to verify your identity, to send out news, offers and advertising to your e-mail address and/or mobile phone via sms, mms or similar messaging system, to tailor content, advertisements and offers we serve you, to improve the Website or to contact you with regard to your use of our Services and the Website. The information regarding your account is used [to deposit money from transactions made when using our Services]. Information submitted may be shared with third parties and transferred to a third country outside the EEA, as further detailed below.

#### 4\. Who has access to your personal data?

We may share your personal data with third parties that perform functions on our behalf, such as for example: companies or individuals that host or operate our Website, analyze data or provide customer service, advertisers, sponsors or other third parties that participate in or administer our promotions or provide marketing or promotional assistance. Your personally identifiable information may also be used by us or shared with our affiliates, sponsors, partners, advertisers or other third parties to provide you with product information and promotional and other offers.

Processing payment transactions requires that we share your personal information with financial institutions that allow us to offer your payment processing services as well as third parties who provide fraud prevention, collections and managed technology services. In connection with your registration on the Website we share your information with verification services and credit bureaus in order to verify your identity.

If your personal data is processed by us or by our third parties, we will ensure that it is protected appropriately and only processed in connection with the services they perform for us in accordance with this privacy policy and applicable data protection legislation.

#### 5\. International Transfers

Personal data provided to us by you may be stored and processed in, and transferred between, any of the countries in which we and our affiliates, agents or contractors have offices, in order to enable us and our affiliates to use that information as set out in this privacy policy. For users of the Sites who are based in the European Union, you should be aware that information which you provide to us may be transferred to countries (including the United States) which do not have data protection laws equivalent to those in force in the European Union.

#### 6\. Links to third party websites

The Website may contain links or references to other websites that we do not operate. When you use these links, you are leaving our Website. We do not control information published on other third party websites and assumes no responsibility for information and other content on such other third party websites. You assume the risk yourself when using other websites linked to this website. We encourage you to review the privacy policy of other websites you visit.

#### 7\. Disclaimer

We reserve the right to disclose your personal data as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our site. We also reserve the right to transfer personal data in connection with the sale, assignment, or other transfer of our business or a portion of our business, including a corporate merger, consolidation, restructuring, sale of assets or other corporate change of our direct or indirect parent companies that affects us.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you. If any changes are unacceptable to you or if you do not accept that we process your personal data in accordance with the revised privacy policy, please contact us by sending a request to [help@izettle.com](mailto:help@izettle.com).

We store personal data for such a period as is prescribed by applicable law. During this period personal data is only used to the extent permitted by these terms and by applicable law as well as for the security of members, that is, in order to prevent, investigate, uncover and prosecute potential crimes against one of our members.

#### 8\. Your choice and access

You may always direct us not to share your personal information with third parties, not to use your personal information to provide you with information or offers, or not to send you newsletters, e-mails or other communications by: (i) sending us an e-mail at [hello@izettle.com](mailto:help@izettle.com), (ii) contacting us by mail at iZettle AB, Kungsg. 9, 111 43 Stockholm, Sweden, or (iii) following the removal instructions in the communication that you receive. Your opt-out request will be processed within 30 days of the date on which we receive it.

If you wish to verify, correct, delete or update any of your personal data collected, you may contact us at the above address or e-mail. In accordance with our routine record keeping, we may delete certain records that contain personal data you have submitted to us. We are under no obligation to store such personal data indefinitely and disclaim any liability arising out of, or related to, the destruction of such personal data. We will not keep personal data for a longer period than what is necessary having regard to the purpose set out in this privacy policy.
